Let's confirm the bond between the director and the manager!
Challenge to guess goods!
Oh!
This time, we're going to the Pokemon Center in Ikebukuro, Tokyo
Mega Tokyo!
Don't get lost now!
I'm going to take the lead!
It's that time of year.
You were waiting for me just now... at the Christmas corner.
Yeah, it was the Christmas corner.
I definitely want one for Christmas!
I found a lot of too cute guess goods!
MiaJ Pokémon Club
Hello everyone!
I'm Ayumi Ozawa and Mizuki Koishida from Mia Re-Call Joy!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
We are starting a new project this time!
Mia Joy's Pokémon project is starting!
Yes!
We did it!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
As Mia Joy Pokemon Club
We are going to enjoy Pokemon as much as we can
while enjoying Pokemon as much as we can.
What? Was this your first club activity?
At once
Our first club activity, Pokemon Club
So, Mia Joy Pokemon club is starting!
I look forward to working with you.
I, Ayumi Ozawa, will be the club leader.
And Mizuki...
I...
What would you like?
Sir...
What?
What's wrong?
I'm afraid we need to talk.
The manager?
Manager...
I'll just say manager-in-chief, then.
Not mentally.
I support Manager Ozawa.
I'll support him.
Yes, sir.
That's fine.
Manager
Great.
I only have two people.
I'm trying to make it bigger.
I'm going to make it big.
I'll do my best too.
Mia Joy Pokemon Club
Yes, that's right, the memorable first project of Mia Joy Pokemon Club is
Let's check the bond between the manager and the director!
Guess the item you like!
Wow, that's great!
So, here we go.
First, you choose 3 items you want to buy today.
And after that, guess what the other person's three guesses will be.
I'd like to guess what they chose.
That's how we'll play the game.
I see.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I forgot.
What's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong?
What's wrong? I didn't see it, but I saw the cup.
Ha-ha-ha.
I see what you mean.
It's hard to buy them, isn't it?
Yes, there are so many goods, and they're so cute.
It's difficult.
But that's exactly what we have to do.
Yeah... the bond...
Because we don't have a bond.
It's worthless.
Let's do our best.
Okay, well, first of all, let's go pick out some goodies we want.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
I'll be there as soon as I can
Miyaji's Pokemon Club
I'll do the same, but Micchan has to guess too
Let's wait a little while to see how Micchan reacts.
We kind of know each other's favorite Pokémon.
Yes, we do.
But there are a lot of things we haven't told each other.
But Micchan is related to you.
The first Pokémon you choose is
I chose Meowha
I chose Kwassu
It's a water type.
I think it will be in demand, too.
I don't think so.
I don't think it's going to be much.
But I love meowha.
Really?
Did you say that?
I love it.
This is the stuffed animal corner.
Let's see how Micchan reacts.
Mr. Kwassu is here.
Oh, really?
I've recently become addicted to him.
I've become a Benimuru.
I'm fine.
I'm still a nyoha
I haven't turned into a masked agen yet.
Oh, it's so cute!
But this season...
It was a very Christmas corner.
Yeah, it was the Christmas corner.
Christmas.
Christmas?
I want to cherish it.
I love Christmas.
I love it.
I love you.
I don't know, Micchan.
But it's a stuffed animal, right?
I'm sure you'll get a stuffed animal.
I'm sure he'll get one.
Micchan...
Thank you for your hard work.
What?
I'm worried.
I heard you're worried about the sports lights.
I just saw it on this view.
Michiko gave it to me for my birthday.
It's from the Seijin Friend series. It's so cute!
I held back then.
And today, it's my birthday present!
Thank you. We're suddenly together again.
Thank you.
I love this "Sleepy Friends" series.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, you should've seen it earlier.
I'll just take a look.
I'll check it out.
I like it a lot.
Oh, well, I'm fine, by the way.
I'm fine.
I'm starting to get it.
You know, sometimes I get this inspiration.
Sometimes you just know it's gonna be this girl.
What?
I don't know.
What does she look like?
She's cute.
What? Me?
But I'm pretty...
Right now.
It's like right now.
I didn't mean to overstep, it's just now.
I was going for it.
I had a pretty good shot.
I was pretty much going for it.
From the beginning?
Yeah, from the beginning.
I saw it on the website and everything before I came.
It's now or never.
So I wanted to get it.
I wanted to get some of them.
Nyanko
I bought Nyanko.
No, but it was certainly an inspiration
I'm glad.
Yes, I am.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Inspiration is important, right?
It's important.
You're being a pain in the ass right now.
Yeah, it is.
She's cute.
I don't know. She's got a prettier face than usual.
You're so cute.
He's cute.
He's so cool.
Cute.
She's like the cute type.
Eh? Mikchan
I think she's cute.
What? I don't think Micchan will go for it.
Huh?
No?
But I dreamed of buying a big stuffed Pokemon doll someday.
A big stuffed Pokemon doll.
That's right.
It's so cute!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Uh, I don't know.
Oh, Fluffy? This is cute.
I'm pretty sure I'm pinching myself.
Yes, you are.
So, this corner, yes.
This corner, yes.
Mr. Ichikanezumi, Mr. Wakkanazumi...
I think it's pretty good.
Accessories are good, too.
They're cute, aren't they?
They're cute.
Well, the accessories are pretty good, too.
Um, they're stylish, so there are designs for everyday use.
So, yes, they're available.
I like this hair clip. It's cute.
Oh, yeah.
You use it all the time.
Yes, I wear it before shows.
Oh, so you have it.
I like accessories, too.
I've been notifying a lot of people.
Yes, when I come here on a private visit.
I buy accessories every time.
Oh, here.
It's cute.
It's cute. It's cute.
It's cute. I love collecting this series.
I sometimes buy a lot, sometimes I cry, sometimes I cry, sometimes I cry, sometimes I cry...
Oh, Nehiyo is so cute!
Oh, you like Nihiyo, don't you, Mi-chan?
I love knee-hillo!
Oh, I'm over here too!
What should I do?
I don't know.
I don't know, but...
I have a stuffed animal.
You have one stuffed animal, right, honey?
Yes, I do.
I'm sure you do.
But that's all I know.
All stuffed animals?
No, not all of them.
Not all of them.
It's pretty important right now.
Right now?
Yeah, now.
This season?
Now.
You too?
I'll give you a last hint.
Last hint.
Uh, but...
Then what?
I'll use it for dinner.
That's a pretty big hint.
That's a pretty good clue.
Okay, I got it.
Dinner.
Okay, everybody, let's see what you want.
Yes!
All right.
Let's start with what you want.
Okay.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, you got it.
Yes, I'm set.
Yes, it's decided.
Here we go.
Sorry my butt is a little too dirty
The one from the Midnight in the Mysterious House collection.
I'm going to make a Christmas stuffed animal for my class.
And I'm going to go with this light-colored tissue case with a cute family mouse.
These are the items I want!
Guess which one I want, Mizuki!
Here are my choices
The stainless steel tumbler "Hermanninfia" and
A fluffy arm pillow plushie of Kapigo.
And a fluffy blanket.
I'm not sure if we're going to be able to get out of here, but this...
But I've given you a lot of hints about the popular tumbler, so I'm hoping you'll guess right.
I made a little show of these two items when we were in the store together.
Highly anticipated!
Miyaji's Pokemon Club
So, we've been looking for our favorite products.
We wanted all of them so much that we were afraid we'd take them all home.
But we've narrowed it down to three.
How do you know? Airin's.
Well, I kind of know everything about Ai-chan.
Oh, that's very encouraging.
I don't know.
It's difficult, I'll try my best.
Okay, I'll try to find out what each other chose this time.
Miyagi Pokemon Club
I'm sure it's this one.
I think it's in this class for sure!
He looks a little frustrated this time of year.
I thought you said you couldn't afford it.
I'll buy it.
I wonder where.
I'll give you something extra.
Class.
One more thing.
Figures. Figures. Figures.
Okay, I'd like to go to the figure section over here.
Ai, Pikachu is my favorite Pokemon.
I think it's one of these figures.
Moon or snow or mysterious night scene in the middle of the night
I think it's one or the other.
This is a cute Pikachu sleeping a little.
This is a cheerful Pikachu
Miss is the one from this happy friend series, Argo.
I said I wanted this girl when we used to hang out together before.
I also got Riolu as a present, so
I'm thinking it might be this girl.
Good night.
I'm going to put in a little hurry.
Well, here's the thing, I don't know... anything.
I don't know anymore. Do you think he'll go?
Do you think it'll go?
But you said you wanted to get a big stuffed Pokemon someday, even if this isn't the right one.
I think this is the way to make that wish come true.
Do you think she'll go?
Emichan, are you going here? Oh no, we have less than a minute left!
He said he wants a stirrup.
The wall should be
Pikachu and Genga mecha...
Mechas too...
He said he wants the case
I said I want the string.
I've got these too.
One at a time.
Oh, you're done with Micchan?
Wow.
What do you mean, "rice"? And, oh, it's already over, isn't it?
I think I'm going to Lizardon, but I wonder if Micchan will venture that far...
What? This phone case and Lizardon...
Give me 10 more seconds, please.
Just 10 more seconds, please!
Did you go already, Micchan? Gone?
I don't care about the size of the ones I want.
Did you go with a bang?
He just went with his feelings.
What?
No, I didn't.
Feeling?
It's a little different.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, I'm not sure.
Pokemon Club of Miyagi
So I've chosen!
It's so hard!
What do you think? Manager Pusiza
Your confidence is manager, isn't it?
Yes, I'm a manager.
Are you confident?
Well, yes.
But I think I guessed right.
Really?
I'm so glad.
I can't wait to see the correct answer.
Oh, my God! I love it.
Well, I hope you have a safe trip.
I don't know what I'm eating.
You said you wanted some? Today.
Well, I mean, did you say you wanted it?
Maybe not today.
But she might have said it on a regular basis.
What?
I don't know.
I'm going to go with this one.
Okay, I'll announce the correct answer right away.
First, I'll tell you how Mizuki guessed what I wanted.
Okay!
Here are the three products I predicted.
Here is the first one!
Oh!
Pikachu in a blanket!
And the second one is the mysterious house at midnight figure.
Oh!
And the last one is here.
Quassle figure!
Quassle's Christmas... what is that?
Oh, that's okay.
It's a stuffed animal.
Oh!
Thank you.
That's nice.
I don't know.
The reason I chose it was because when we were going around the store together.
I was looking at this Pikachu with such love in my eyes.
I knew I had to have him.
And this Kwastle is also Ai's partner of choice.
That's right.
Well, I think she chose him.
And finally, this Pikachu blanket.
It's a must have for this time of the year.
What?
I said, hey...
I don't know...
What did you say?
What did I just say?
Maybe I didn't say anything.
Correct answer.
Oh! What? You already announced the correct answer?
What? That's a big surprise.
Oh, my God! I'm so nervous!
Here are the 3 items I want!
Turn!
Oh!
Aaah!
Mayama-kun's mysterious mansion!
Oh, no! This!
The class Christmas stuffed animal
And consistently designed tea stick art!
That one!
But I won two out of three!
What?
But I wanted this one so bad, too!
I was on the edge of my seat.
What? Really?
Really?
Wait a minute.
You're too good a manager.
Sweaty.
Hey!
Oh, my gosh! That's amazing!
And you guessed it, just like this Christmas.
Hey!
I mean, it would be awesome to win this.
I know you had a lot of trouble with this collection.
This is where I spend most of my time.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
I was given the choice between a really fluffy pastel one...
Or something stone-like?
Oh!
But I really like the face of Pikachu.
I really like the dark look of this one.
So, I decided to go with the darker type.
Wow!
Really?
No, just blow it off!
Oh, my God!
No!
Thank you!
Oh, my God!
I can't wait to meet your mistress.
Oh, man!
I'll do my best! Sir.
Yes, sir!
Now then...
I would like to announce what Mizuki wants!
Ahh...
It's a prediction, isn't it?
I'm so nervous!
No, my manager is too good.
I'm most confident.
Yeah!
Well, I'll see you at the end.
Yes! - Yes!
Okay, here's my first choice!
Well, then!
I chose the Metamon strap for my phone!
You know, when we were going around together like this...
Oh! I might want to get a strap.
Then he gave me a sideways glance
She threw me a sideways glance.
I believe Mizuki at that moment.
Yes, I do! I believe you.
Yes, I do!
And the explanation! This way!
Yes!
Oh!
What?
Chopsticks!
I think these are chopsticks.
I'm for rice! He said "rice".
I didn't understand. I left the meditation forest.
Sorry.
So when you say rice, you mean chopsticks!
Yes, yes...
And since Micchan chose "Nyanha" for this game...
So I chose these grass chopsticks!
So cute!
And now the last one!
Ready, set, go!
Yes! This way!
This is...
When you let me go to the Pokemon Center with you...
Ayumi... just now...
He gave me a Lior as a gift.
Micchan wanted this one, but he was holding back, so I think he might want it this time.
These three.
I don't know.
Mine then.
I'll tell you what I want.
I'd like to announce what I want.
I'm nervous.
Here we go.
Here you go.
The correct answer is here!
Ta-da!
Oh?
Stealth Tumbler L. Nephia.
Nephia?
Aah!
Fluffy arm-pillow camera!
Yay!
Yeah! Yeah!
What else?
The last one.
The fluffy blanket stand-in.
A scapegoat.
Three items, right here.
Oh, my God! But!
But!
Oh, I want those, too!
Really?
Thank you!
You're right, Nephia.
Yeah, but I don't think you're supposed to smell it.
What?
There's no such thing as a smell.
But I want lots of blankets.
Did you say that?
Did I?
Then it's your responsibility.
Good luck, sir.
Wow, you both won!
Tumbler!
Rice. Is this rice?
This is rice.
He wants a glass.
I'll tell him slowly.
I'll say it slowly.
What?
Huh? It's difficult.
I'm lost, Mr. Miserd.
But you know, it's difficult, isn't it?
It's difficult.
I don't know...
But I've been wanting to welcome this kabigo since the last time I went to the new moon, so...
I'll give you a cup for everyone.
If you do this cup once...
This cup is also Kabigo
It's so cute!
Feels good
Yes, so the result is
Michi won two cups, and Manager Daishida won two cups.
I guessed two, and I, the manager, was able to guess one.
I was able to guess one.
But I'm very energetic.
Good luck!
Thank you so much!
How was it? Today, again.
I had a lot of fun.
We had a lot of fun, and we got to come to our favorite Pokemon Center together.
It was a lot of fun.
I really love it.
I'm so excited to be able to show it on YouTube.
It was a dream come true and I've been so excited all the time.
Thank you so much!
Let's work hard again.
I'm going to keep working hard and have fun with you, Micchan.
I don't know when our next activity will be.
I don't know when our next club activity will be, but please look forward to it!
I'd like to try playing Pokemon cards.
I'd like to try my hand at it.
I hope we can do it someday.
Shall we? Sure, I'd like to play a lot.
If there is something you want us to do in the Pokemon club, please let us know.
If you have any project you'd like us to do, please let us know in the comments section.
Please let us know in the comments section.
Please let us know!
Okay, that's all for now.
This is the Pokemon Club of Miyaju!
Bye bye!
ED